We've got a killer top lane matchup.
The perfect opportunity for the new
Volibear. In this patch, Riot added
attack damage scaling to Volibear's
passive, but that was just one of four
buffs they gave AD Voli in 2026. The
result? His Q scales with 160%AD, his
Ult with 250%, and his W. Based on my
math, I think we're reaching nearly 300
%. I talked to Joseph Morovoli and I'll
try to show you the best build I can
imagine for him right now.
>> Follow me. We'll bring the house down,
>> family. Right now, with Doran's and
Lethal Tempo, he's the strongest level
one in the top lane, so we have to
respect that. Especially since Voli is
good at level two, right? No, level one
. Took the minions, back off. You can
give up some farm, okay? It's no
problem. Going in, he'll exhaust us and
keep auto-attacking. Because Doran's
Ring is just for the mana, man. Voli's
mana here, combined with Presence of
Mind, gets perfect. And keep applying
the pressure. No rush, bro. Nothing
beats a patient guy, man. Like I said,
look. Get your minions. Easy. Strip his
passive now, look. One attack, poof.
Oops, didn't hit. Now it hit. Deal
damage and back off. Then hit him if he
wants to stay, we aren't weak either.
Conqueror stacked. His W starts scaling
really hard with AD. Walk at him. Take
the shield, honestly. If you don't hit
him. That's fine. Eat him up. Perfect.
If I could time the E right, I could
have dived. It went through even with
exhaust, Voli's damage is ridiculous,
kid. See guys, when you cast E, the E
takes two seconds to land and your Q
takes one. So, you have to wait at
least one second to be able to land the
combo. And our first item, very
important, will be Eclipse, which was
buffed from 6 to 8%of the target's
health. It's ridiculous, man. Once you
finish this item, bro. Nobody beats you
, above all else. So, just the fact
that Voli can build it now already
increases the champion's potential. And
now is where our work comes in to
freeze or do the famous slow push; once
you've gained an advantage over him,
you get that benefit. It's the reward
for crushing your opponent. And I deal
some damage here, look, he messed up.
He's trying to clear the wave. Just
wait, let it tank. There. And since he
rushed boots, we have to rush them too
to match the movement speed, or you'll
get banned. Volibear tiger skin. Worse
is that we really are a tiger, man. The
"bed" was banned, right? True. My bad.
The worst part is I got coached by
Curtesy. He's the best in Brazil, and
actually, in the world. He told me the
worst matchup for Yasuo is Voli. That
he bans him because few people play
Voli in Brazil. Walk up, catch him,
walk into the shield and hit him. And
hit him. Cancel his tornado with your
ult, very important. And when he
cancels our Q too, it comes back,
because that's how it works. And we
have it again to chase him down. Every
time you use crowd control on
Volibear's Q, it ends up resetting the
skill. But it has to be hard CC, right?
It can't be a slow, for example. Got
him. Look there. See how his E gets
stopped in the middle of the way? It's
like Veigar's cage that also does that
with dashes. Close it and prepare
yourself, dude. Alright. Keep hitting,
keep hitting. He died. I don't even
need to do anything else. Just the
Eclipse damage with the W is already
enough, actually. Let's go, dragon,
fight for this, man. If we can get this
dragon, we buy time to scale peacefully
. I'm already starting on Trinity Force
, which is the second item. Come here,
Veigar. Come here, VEIGAR. Caught him.
Take some healthy damage already. Man,
honestly, I wish she would B. Just go
mid so she stays safer. It doesn't
matter if it's against Irelia or Yasuo,
you know? I can play against both just
fine. There's a ward here. Stunned him.
Stunned you. Nice. He didn't expect the
big bear. See how you're already
transitioning the advantage? "Oh man, I
win lane, but I can't win the game."
You have to think, damn it. You saw
that I have flash. Got him. Geez, it's
no use. Ult. Look at how the damage is
already. Look at how it's getting
interesting. The ult is already doing
761, the W 636. But that's not even
close to what will happen, guys. You
are going to like these numbers. And
since the passive now scales with AD,
man, it's really chill to clear waves
without using many abilities, you know?
Also. Ready. Ah, I died, man. Oh, I
took the tower. Triforce finished. And
let's start the fun, with two items
that are actually just one, right?
Which is Death's Dance along with
another friend. What's the big plan?
What's the plan, Ionizão? Uzão.
Ionizão, you're fed, you have almost
three items, brother, and you won't
trade with me. Oh, he didn't see that
I'm just about to unleash D, guys. He
thought I was little, cute, passive,
harmless. It's not W, it's W in the
face. Take that, take the tower. And my
team is winning over there. How
beautiful, man. Go team, go, make
history. And we aren't taking the Inhib
, okay guys? It's really bad to take an
inhib this early, it just gives the
guys free farm. Never take the inhib.
You have to analyze the situation. It's
not like Dota, right? In Dota, you take
the inhib and the minions start giving
less resources, which is how it should
be. And we finished Death's Dance. Man,
this really changes the champion,
because since we have so much shield
and healing, Death's Dance brings the
damage so we can heal and shield
through it. And then, he'll try to
escape, but we get them out of position
and that's enough. Man, look at the
damage my W is doing, dude. What a
broken thing, man. Guys, go, go, dragon
, go dragon. I'll TP to that. Just
leave one more here. Or I could go for
the GG, guys. Ah, I'll TP there, man.
Let's fight this. Go. I want to test my
potential. Take it then. I like that.
Oh, no. The bite came out. The worst
part is I could've finished the game
here and I came for the dragon just for
the laughs. But if we end it now, we
won't see the Voli with eternal hunger,
right? Hi, Dianinha. Hi, Kawaii. How
much is our W at now? 112 damage. Our W
is at 221%AD without Conqueror stacked.
Bite. Come here, he's only alive
because of Death's Dance. One's already
dead. Come here, the other brother,
come the other brother. Bite another.
Easy. Calm, calm, hold on, because look
, you have to respect the history. Bite
everyone, kid. Come back here, come
back here, samurai. Come back here, kid
. Oh, the game is going to end, guys.
We won't find out the total damage. I
don't have TP. Oh, but it was already
over 1000 damage just on our bite, okay
? But with a full build, I predict we
can reach 1500, because there's also
Gathering Storm, many things. Let's
look for a more challenging opponent.
Would you like some orange juice to go
with your meal? It's all yours, go
ahead. But don't forget to like,
subscribe to the channel, and leave a
comment down below. Now I'll continue
with the video. We'll bring the sky
down.
>> Family. I don't even need to say we
lose level 1, right? Just chill and
let's wait for that level 2. Alright.
Take the Q. Start stacking the passive.
Hit the Q and get out. Getting the
passive. You can play it and keep
taking it. There. Now the lane is ours.
Getting boots early to kite better and
start the Eclipse. Alright. I like that
. I really like that. Guys, is there
any difficulty? There isn't, man. Just
trust the big bear. I miss when she
called me "cuddly bear." Calm down. The
problem with remembering the ex is that
you only remember the good stuff. You
have to remember the bad things too.
You can't have selective memory. Take
that, take that, take that. What's the
plan? 38, man. There. Okay, he already
ulted. You're shocked, aren't you, son?
You're shocked. Hungry. And now what
are you going to do? Amumu, you are
really bad. Hit your Qs, buddy. No need
to talk to him like that. The game was
good for us, now it's bad. My team, man
. One play, one play. Come here. I'm
going to follow you, brother. There's
nowhere for you to go. Done, Singed is
top, but I think he's going to base.
Fighting me now is madness. And
actually, at any point in the game it
will be very difficult, because it only
gets worse. Done. Let's go for the
third item. Alright, alright. Good,
good angle for a fight. Try to get them
in the middle, in the middle, Amumu.
Flash, flash Amumu. Wow! Take that. And
here comes the next one. And here comes
the next one. Alright. Everyone blew
their flashes there too, man. My team
is so bizarre that Olaf managed to take
an inhibitor. That's wild, man. I'm
speechless. And the worst part is that
what he did was great for us, because
now I have a place to farm infinitely
and he won't be able to farm because
he'll always be pushing against us. And
with Death's Dance finished at 20
minutes, with Gathering Storm not even
really kicking in yet, at 1162 damage.
Let's go for Eternal Hunger. Hey family
, can we start this Baron instead of
calling FF? My God, he stole it.
>> He stole it. How, man? It's four
against one. How did they let him get
into the pit to steal it? It wasn't
even close, brother. This game is risky
, man.
>> Come easy. Volibear. Come easy. There's
hunger. Come easy. Hello hunger. Come
easy. Hello hunger. Let me get out of
here, please. Thanks. Everything showed
up here. It's no use for me to flash or
anything. They arrived really fast
because they have the Baron recall that
Kha'Zix stole, but that's okay. Let's
give up this Baron, let's focus on the
soul, the soul point, and everything
will be fine. And with the fourth item,
family, our ult is at 1361 and the W,
boy. 1200 on a W. I just want to fight
now, man. And that's without stacking
Conqueror. Worth remembering. The five
of them come nicely, bunched up like
five bronzies and it works out. There's
no way to fail, man. Look, take
Banshee's off this guy, it helps me a
lot, bro. Where is this guy, man? Where
the hell is the team? I healed there,
man. But he was on fourth heal. Why are
there four, five people hitting me, man
? And my team is who knows where, man.
Man, that doesn't have to mean anything
, right? It's only their second dragon.
But it's concerning. Main, you told
them to go like five bronzies, and they
did. My fault then, man. I apologize.
Look, caught Jhin. Jhin. He's here,
look. Get Seraphine. No more CC left.
Good, Jhin and Seraphine's flashes are
gone. Let's turn here. Let's turn here,
guys. The W is over there in bot. Man,
I zoned the guy there. Wait, you can't
zone with a control mage. Look at that
jungle movement. Ok, ok. He has a plan.
Look at big Kha'Zix. Kha'Zix is there,
man. It's gonna be. He stole it again.
No, no, it's impossible, it's
impossible, it's impossible. I need
more tenacity, guys. Let's go here. The
W is dealing 1500, man. The W is
dealing 1500. I just need to be able to
play. If I can actually play the fight,
guys, it's so annoying against them
when they have flash, because they have
Seraphine, Janna, and so many champs to
peel me off, and Khazix goes invisible.
It's beautiful. Look at that, guys. The
W is doing more damage than the ult
because the AD scaling is at 253%.
Again, without Conqueror stacked. I'm
gonna push top, man. I'll force someone
from them to recall. Check the tower.
Someone from them went back, damn.
It’s Seraphine, maybe one more. Yeah,
someone else flickered there. I’m
gonna bail since Janna might be there
too. And they are killing Olaf. Oh my
god, everyone is here, dude. Please,
please, Janna don't cancel me. She
ulted.
>> What now, Janna? What now, Jhin? What
now, kid? What are you gonna do, damn
it? When my W is Cho'Gath's ult, you
bastard. Look at my health, man. Look
at the heal. Look at the heal we just
got, man. Because of Death's Dance.
Volibear's W. You have to respect AD
Voli, man. AP Voli doesn't do this,
dude. Sorry for getting worked up, guys
. I had a lot bottled up here. But run,
huh? Her flash again. One more time.
Keep the passive alive.
>> Guys, why are you, why are you scared?
We don't...
>> went for dragon.
>> Why did we go for dragon, man? We
should've just finished. Ahri recalled.
Amumu went for dragon. 486 AD, 1600 on
the W and rising. Screw it, let's play
this forever. They're enjoying the game
, man. And the Q, what about it? Damn,
the Q is hitting for 1100 too. I had
forgotten about it. It's 1100 on the Q,
1600 on the W and 1600 on the ult. Get
that Janna, go. She's gonna get slowed
anyway. She won't escape. Thank you,
guys. Can we now, please, end the game.
There are two dead. They only have one
Nexus tower left. It’s literally just
walk in. There, Khazix is already dead.
Jhin is ulting from the base out of
fear. He got slowed. Destroying it.
>> Look, Seraphine is already ulting for
no reason. I’m gonna hit that Nexus,
man. I don't care, man. I don't care.
I’m already happy with my 1600 damage
W. I'm not waiting 40 minutes for the
rising storm for K. So now I ask, is
there any other volleyball build you
think I should do? Let me know in the
comments.